http://www.colonialtimes.com/content/2-privacy-policy

Your Account
ClocksGrandfather ClocksGrandmother ClocksWall ClocksMantel ClocksAlarm ClocksTable Top ClocksOutdoor ClocksWeather / MaritimeCuckoo Clocks8-Day Cuckoo Clock1-Day Cuckoo ClockQuartz Cuckoo ClockPlaquesClock KitsGrandfather Clock KitsClock ComponentsMovement PackagesMovementsGlobesFloor GlobesDesk GlobesEducation GlobesWatchesMistura WatchesMusic/Motion ClocksRhythm Wall ClocksRhythm Mantel ClocksRhythm Alarm Clocks
Cart
0
products
product
(empty)
No products
CAD$0.00
Shipping
CAD$0.00
Total:
Cart
Home
>
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Colonial Times Clock Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the www.colonialtimes.com website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Colonial Times Clock.
Personal identification
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information.
Users may however visit our Site anonymously.
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
How we use collected information
Colonial Times Clock Inc. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:
To improve customer serviceYour information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
To personalize user experienceWe may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
To improve our SiteWe continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process transactionsWe may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site featureTo send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
To send periodic emailsThe email address Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. We will at no time sell your information.
Sensitive and private data exchanged between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.
Third party websites
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.
Changes to this privacy policy
Colonial Times Clock Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Colonial Times Clock Inc. 20 Benjamin RoadWaterloo, Ontario N2V 2J9519-884-2511info@colonialtimes.com
Shop
Clocks
Grandfather Clocks
Grandmother Clocks
Wall Clocks
Mantel Clocks
Alarm Clocks
Table Top Clocks
Sign up to receive special offers and promotions from Colonial Times.
Our sister company:
Copyright © 2013 Colonial Times Clock Inc. / Terms of Use / Privacy Policy
